

Senior Graphic Designer with 4+ years of designing and directing successful campaigns, National publishings, and developing print/digital designs for the owner and operator of Gallery Furniture. Customer satisfaction, expedited work-paced environment, proven creativity and consistent quality enveloped by certified Concept Keys, Inc. listening skills, bilingual proficiency, and a strong desire to exceed expectations for the ultimate customer experience.

## EXPERIENCE

## Senior Graphic Designer at Gallery Furniture - Houston, TX September 2012 - Present Day

Creative Direction; primary decision maker for font(s), colors, photographs and metrics used for brand awareness.

Lead conceptual development for local and national ads, email marketing campaigns and in-store signage.

Team Management; creative support and review of all marketing materials including 2014 revamp of the ecommerce

Gallery Furniture website. Member of corporate presentation team responsible for speaking with the owner.

Print & Digital Advertisement; responsible for dispursement and placement of ads including all social media outlets.

#### Freelance Designer - Houston, TX August 2011 - Present Day

Brand Identity; designing the logo and overall image of the company by identifying the goal of the client. Print & Digital Advertisement; draft to print for flyers, brochures, gift cards, and Google listings. Photography; studio and location photography produced for marketing efforts. Interactive Design; HTML5/CSS coded website including optimized images for faster loading times.

## SXSW Production Crew - Austin, TX Spring 2012

**Promoter;** assisted artist(s) to the venues.

#### EDUCATION

# Bachelor of Fine Arts with Honors - Communication Design School of Art & Design | Texas State University Dean's List 2010-2012

## ACCOLADES

### Campaign Advertisement

Lead design efforts for successful promotions such as Superbowl Promotion(s), Houston Astros Outfield Ad(s), NASCAR Stock Car Design, 85 and its FREE

## Multi-National & Local Publications

Cowboys & Indians, Luxe Magazine, Houston Chronicle, Better Homes, Buzz Magazine, VYPE Magazine, Richmond Magazine

### Poster for Tomorrow - Summer 2011

Shortlisted in the International Competition for the Right to Education Cause

### SKILLS

Professional proficiency with Adobe Creative Suite
Experience leading photographers, graphic artists, and copywriters
Product & Journalism Photography including Infomercial Audio / Videography
Intermediate Knowledge of HTML5 / CSS
Certified Concept Keys, Inc. Listening Skills
Strong written and verbal communication in English and Spanish